[
    {"problem": "웰컴 투", "answer": "동막골", "type": "text"},
    {"problem": "어바웃", "answer": "타임", "type": "text"},
    {"problem": "엽기적인", "answer": "그녀", "type": "text"},
    {"problem": "이웃집", "answer": "토토로", "type": "text"},
    {"problem": "쥬라기", "answer": "월드", "type": "text"},
    {"problem": "쥬라기", "answer": "공원", "type": "text"},
    {"problem": "찰리와 초콜릿", "answer": "공장", "type": "text"},
    {"problem": "천공의 성", "answer": "라퓨타", "type": "text"},
    {"problem": "태극기", "answer": "휘날리며", "type": "text"},
    {"problem": "토이", "answer": "스토리", "type": "text"},
    {"problem": "해리포터와 불사조", "answer": "기사단", "type": "text"},
    {"problem": "나홀로", "answer": "집에", "type": "text"},
    {"problem": "내 이름은", "answer": "김삼순", "type": "text"},
    {"problem": "마이너리티", "answer": "리포트", "type": "text"},
    {"problem": "말할 수 없는", "answer": "비밀", "type": "text"},
    {"problem": "바람과 함께", "answer": "사라지다", "type": "text"},
    {"problem": "사운드 오브", "answer": "뮤직", "type": "text"},
    {"problem": "살인의", "answer": "추억", "type": "text"},
    {"problem": "세", "answer": "얼간이", "type": "text"},
    {"problem": "친절한", "answer": "금자씨", "type": "text"},
    {"problem": "해리포터와 죽음의", "answer": "성물", "type": "text"},
    {"problem": "인사이드", "answer": "아웃", "type": "text"},
    {"problem": "유주얼", "answer": "서스펙트", "type": "text"},
    {"problem": "어메이징", "answer": "스파이더맨", "type": "text"},
    {"problem": "비긴", "answer": "어게인", "type": "text"},
    {"problem": "수상한", "answer": "그녀", "type": "text"},
    {"problem": "동갑내기", "answer": "과외하기", "type": "text"},
    {"problem": "팔월의", "answer": "크리스마스", "type": "text"},
    {"problem": "은밀하게", "answer": "위대하게", "type": "text"}
]